Chandrakant Dilip Sangale

Bachelor in Computer Application 2017

Shahada, MH | +91-9420854189 | c.sangale@gmail.com

ncds.github.io ncds.github.com/cds

Summary

An industry expert in Website Development with an excellent understanding of MVC/MVVP techniques and WordPress CMS, Javascript, and Various languages used in Development operations. Security-focused Design with an approach to using Bootstrap and MVC & MVVM patterns.

• Ensure smooth business operations by following projects from conceptualizing phase to completion, including system design, incorporation of customer needs and technical support.

Work experience

Web Developer 2019 - Present

Enlight Technologies - Shahada, MH

Web Development And Web Hosting Company - Shahada, MH

Web Developer- Intern 2017 - 2018

Aspirio - Nashik, MH

Web Development Company

Team Lead 2017 - 2018

Amtech(CRM)- Nashik, MH

Customer Relationship Management Software Company

Education

Bachelor In Computer Application 2014 - 2017

Pune University

Commerce, Management & Computer Science (CMCS) College

HSC 2009 - 2011

Nashik Board

Sheth V. K. Shah Vidya Mandir and Kau Sau G.F Patil Junior College, Shahada.

SSC 2008 - 2009

Nashik Board

Tapi Valley English Medium School, Shahada.

Projects

(MVP)s

Todo App: Node-Express-MongoDB-Vue: Developed with Node-Express-MongoDB-Vue Scaliable to-do app deployed on Heroku

Goal App: Node-Express-MongoDB-Nuxt: Created with Aim of Socialize the Goals. It is easily scalable, used jwt token for the authentication, design by Bootstrap CSS, Deployed frontend, backend on different server, with GitHub integration.

SKILLS

FRAMEWORK

- Vue/ Nuxt (<1 Year)
- Bootstrap (3 years)
- Express (<1 Year)

LANGUAGE

- HTML (4 years)
- CSS (4 years)
- Javascript (4 years)
- MySQL (3 years)
- MongoDB (<1 year)

APPLICATION

- Git
- Photoshop
- Bootstrap Studio

CMS

• Wordpress (3 years)

RELEVANTCOURSEWORK

Object-Oriented Programming Web-based Information Technology Computer Graphics Artificial Intelligence Database Systems Functional Programming Operating Systems Systems Software